Leach, W. Barton (Walter Barton), 1900 -1971. Papers, 1920-1971: Finding Aid.
Papers, 1920-1971.
Harvard Law School Library, Harvard University
HOLLIS 601669
Leach, W. Barton (Walter Barton), 1900-1971
66 boxes.
Contents of this collection relate to Leach's teaching career, professional activities, service in the Air Force during World War II, and involvement in national defense matters. Includes material relating to his role as consultant to the Air Force, 1946-1966, his work with Harvard University's Defense Policy Seminar, which he founded, and drafts of an incomplete autobiography.
The papers of Walter Barton Leach, professor of law, legal scholar, and consultant on military affairs to the U.S. Government and the Armed Services, were presented as a gift to the President and Fellows of Harvard College by Professor Leach's widow, Blanche C. Leach. The letter of gift, dated 24 October 1972, states that this gift "is intended for the use and benefit of the Harvard Law School".
Access to these papers is governed by the rules and regulations of the Harvard Law School Library. This collection is open to the public, but is housed off-site at Harvard Depository and requires 2-day advance notice for retrieval. Consult the Special Collections staff for further information.
In addition, access is governed by the terms of access as set forth by Mrs. Blanche C. Leach in her letter of October 24, 1972, addressed to professor Morris L. Cohen, Librarian of the Harvard Law School Library (for copy see Case File).
The 16,000 items in the papers of Walter Barton Leach (1900-1971) span the years 1920 to 1971, with the bulk of the papers falling within the 1940 to 1970 period. The collection includes correspondence; memoranda; minutes of meetings; reports; transcripts; press releases; government and other forms and form letters; official documents; legislative bills; financial statements; drafts and outlines of speeches and writings; typed manuscripts; proof sheets; lecture notes; lists; tables; news clippings; printed items; photographs; one phonograph record.
The papers of Walter Barton Leach relate to his professional life and activities as law teacher and legal scholar (1930-1971); his service in the American Air Forces during World War II (1942-1945); his role as a consultant to the U.S. Air Force and the U.S. Department of the Air Force (1946-1966); his founding and work with the so-called Defense Policy Seminar, established at Harvard University in 1954; and his involvement in national defense matters beginning in the early 1950's. There are drafts of several sections of an autobiography which 4dBL had planned but which was not completed. The Leach Papers also include manuscripts of most of his published and unpublished speeches and occasional pieces such as anecdotes and poems.
The correspondence files of WBL include both letters received and carbons of letters sent. There is a complete file of carbons, the so-called "dictation file", in chronological order, covering the years 1958 through 1970; carbons are bound, each volume covering a six-months' period. Among Professor Leach's correspondents were:
Robert Amory
Robert R. Bowie
Edward W. Brooke
Harold Brown
Joseph S. Clark
James B. Conant
Archibald Cox
R, Ami Cutter
James If. Douglas
Robert F. Drinan
Trevor N. Dupuy
Herbert B. Ehrmann
Thomas K. Fin letter
Felix Frankfurter
James M, Gavin
Arthur L. Goodhart
Murray Green
John M, Harlan
Christin A. Herter
Edward F. Kennedy
John Fitzgerald Kennedy (President of the U.S.)
Robert F. Kennedy
Henry A. Kissinger
Laurence S. Kuter
Curtis E. LeMay
Henry Cabot Lodge, Jr.
James K, Logan
Glen W, Martin
Bernard Law Montgomery (Field Marshal)
Lauris Norstad
Frank Pace, Jr.
Thomas S. Power
Nathan M. Pusey (President of Harvard University)
Donald A. Quarles
Fred Rodell
Leverett Saltonstall
Sir John C. Slessor
Stuart Symington
Telford Taylor
Barbara Tuchman
Nathan B. Twining
Hoyt S. Vandenberg
Raymond S. Wilkins
Charles E. Wyzanski, Jr
Eugene M, Zuckert.
Series List/Description
This collection is grouped into two contingencies. The first is arranged in eight series. The second is arranged into four of the initial given eight series.
Contingent I.
Series I. General Correspondence (Unbound)
Correspondence is mainly of a professional nature. Topics discussed in the letters include publications by WBL and by his correspondents, employment matters of former students, national defense matters in general way, studies at Harvard and other places in the field of military defense.
Correspondents include professional colleagues, persons in Massachusetts and national politics, Harvard alumni, news media editors, members of the armed services of the United States and Great Britain. Correspondence consists of letters received and carbons of letters sent. A substantial amount of correspondence is with various members of the Center for International Affairs at Harvard University, a division under the Graduate School of Public Administration. In 1954, WBL helped establish the Defense Policy Seminar at the Center, and he was instrumental in procuring many of the Seminar's guest lecturers such as Field Marshall Montgomery. Of interest are the folders relating to WBL's activity as an advisor to John F. Kennedy during the 1960 presidential election.
Important correspondents: U.S. Senators Joseph Clark, Edward Brooke and Stuart Symington, U.S. Supreme Court Justices Felix Frankfurter and John Harlan, Henry Kissinger, Sir John Slessor, Telford Taylor, and Barbara Tuchman.
Series II. General Correspondence (Bound)
This is a so-called "dictation file" of carbons of letters sent out by WBL. Carbons were bound in chronological order, each volume convering six months of a given year. The period covered is January 1, 1958 to December 31, 1970. In content, the series is similar to the unbound correspondence series.
Series III. Teaching Notes
This series relates primarily to courses on Property (conveyancing, wills, future interests, perpetuities) with some material on Evidence and Contracts. Boxes 19-24 contain loose-leaf books filled with notes and assignments. Boxes 25 and 26 contain unbound notes, correspondence with students, and material for a manual (never published) for law students.
Series IV. Writings and Research
This series relates to books, articles and speeches by WBL and to material on perpetuity reform throughout the world. It consists of notes, drafts, research material, final typewritten manuscripts and reprints of some of WBL's writings and speeches as well as correspondence about specific subjects or specific pieces of writing. A substantial part of this series deals with the three casebooks (on wills, property and future interests) put together by WBL, alone or in conjunction with others.
This series begins with books by WBL, arranged alphabetically by author or co-author. Speeches and articles are then arranged chronologically by date of publication or delivery. Research material on perpetuities reform is at the end, arranged alphabetically.
Series V. Defense Studies
The major portion of the material in this series concerns matters relating to the Defense Policy Seminar which WBL helped establish at Harvard in 1954. Other groups of material deal with WBL's involvement in national defense matters beginning in the early 1950's, and with articles and speeches of WBL advocating a strong defense force. The material has been left in its original arrangement. Dates covered are 1951-1966.
Series VI. Harvard Miscellany
This series consists of correspondence with colleagues, speeches at meetings of Harvard Clubs and Harvard Law School Associations throughout the country, and material relating to the Harvard Law Review, the Harvard Law School Model Trial, the Leach Club, and other Harvard University activities. Period covered is 1930-1970.
Series VII. Biographical and Other Miscellany
This series contains clippings, photographs, correspondence, and typewritten drafts for a proposed autobiography (unpublished) by WBL. There is a good deal of material relating to his activities in the United States Air Force; also a section on legal poetry. The series is arranged alphabetically.
Series VIII. U.S. Air Force
Professor Leach's Air Force files consist chiefly of material relating to his service with the American Air Forces during World War II and subsequently with the United States Air Force, both active service and service after retirement. Files include his reports and memoranda relating to operations analysis; material relating to his work as a consultant; appointments and travel orders; correspondence concerning special missions; material relating to investigations of particular strategic weapons or aircraft; recommendations regarding the U.S. Air Force Academy at Colorado Springs and other Air Force schools.
The series contains a sizeable amount of correspondence with various staff officers. Among Professor Leach's major correspondents are: Harold Brown, James B. Conant, James H. Douglas, Jr., Thomas K. Finletter, Murray Green, Henry A. Kissinger, Laurence S. Kuter, Curtis S. Power, Donald A. Quarles, Stuart Symington, Nathan P. Twining, Hoyt S. Vandenberg, Eugene M. Zuckert.
All of this material is now de-classified.
Contingent II.
Series IX. General Correspondence (Unbound)
Series X. Defense Studies
Series XI. Harvard Miscellany
Series XII. Air Force
Historical/Biographical Information
January 6, 1900 b. Boston, Massachusetts. s. Walter Barton and Grace Winifred (Wise) L.
1921 A.B., cum laude, Harvard University
Summer 1920 Graduate student, Universite de Grenoble,
1924 LL.B., cum laude, Harvard Law School
1924 m, Florence T. Malcolm; divorced, 1941
1944 m. Jane Mcllwraith; deceased, 1963
1964 m. Blanche C. Bartlett
1924-1925 Secretary to Justice Oliver Wendell Holmes, Jr., U.S. Supreme Court
1925 Admitted to Massachusetts bar
1925-1930 Engaged in general practice of law in Boston, associated with the firm of Warner, Stackpole Bradlee
1929 Instructor in law, Harvard Law School
1930 Assistant professor of law, Harvard Law School
1931-1960 Professor of law, Harvard Law School
1960-1969 Story Professor of law, Harvard Law School
1954-1969 Professor, Harvard Graduate School of Public Administration
1952 Visiting professor, Oxford University
1947 Consultant to U.S.A.F.
1918 Served as private, Infantry, U.S. Army
June 1942 Commissioned major, U.S. Army
January, 1943 Lt. col. Air Corps
August, 1944 Col., Air Corps
1949 Brig, general, 11.5. Air Force Reserve
1945 Legion of Merit
1949 Exceptional Civilian Service Award
December 15, 1971 d. Waltham, Massachusetts
Author of:
Cases on Future Interest, 1935
Cases on Massachusetts Law of Evidence, 1935
Cases on Mills, 1939; revised edition, 1960
Handbook of Massachusetts Evidence, 1940; the third edition (with John T. McNaughton), 1956; 4th edition with Paul J. Liacos, 1967)
Cases and Text on Property (with A. James Casner), 1950; second edition, (with A. James Casner), 1969
The Rule against, Perpetuities (England, with J.Ii.C. Morris), 1955
The Rule against Perpetuities (U.S., with Owen Tudor), 1957
Cases and Text on Future Interests and Estate Planning, 1961 (with J, K. Logan)
Also author of articles in legal and other periodicals
Co-author of American Law of Property, 1952
Additional Index Terms
The following catalog entries represent persons, organizations, and topics documented in this collection. An entry for each appears in the Harvard On Line Library Information System (HOLLIS) and other automated bibliographic databases. THIS IS NOT AN INDEX.
Amory, Robert, 1915-; Bowie, Robert R.; Brooke, Edward William, 1919-; Brown, Harold, 1915-; Clark, Joseph S.; Conant, James Bryant, 1893-1978; Cox, Archibald, 1912-; Cutter, R. Ammi.; Douglas, James H.; Drinan, Robert F.; Dupuy, Trevor Nevitt, 1916-; Ehrmann, Herbert B. (Herbert Brutus), 1891-; Finletter, Thomas Knight, 1893-; Frankfurter, Felix, 1882-1965.; Gavin, James Maurice, 1907-; Goodhardt, Arthur Lehman.; Green, Murray G.; Harlan, John M. (John Marshall), 1899-1971; Herter, Christian Archibald, 1895-1966; Kennedy, Edward Moore, 1932-; Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963.; Kennedy, Robert F. 1925-1968.; Kissinger, Henry, 1923-; Kuter, Laurence S.; Leach, W. Barton (Walter Barton), 1900-; LeMay, Curtis E.; Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1902-; Logan, James K.; Martin, Glen W. O.; Montgomery of Alamein, Bernard Law Montgomery, Viscount,; Norstad, Lauris; Pace, Frank; Power, Thomas S.; Pusey, Nathan Marsh, 1907-; Quarles, Donald A.; Rodell, Fred, 1907-; Saltonstall, Leverett, 1892-; Slessor, John Cotesworth, Sir, 1897-; Symington, Stuart; Taylor, Telford; Tuchman, Barbara Wertheim; Twining, Nathan B.; Vandenberg, Hoyt S.; Wilkins, Raymond S.; Wyzanski, Charles E. (Charles Edward), 1906-; Zuckert, Eugene M.; Harvard University - Defense Policy Seminar; Law teachers; United States - Air Force; United States - Defenses
CONTAINER LIST
Within each series individual items or folders are identified by box and folder number. For example, the number 5-12 corresponds to box 5, folder 12.
- CONTINGENT I
  - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE (UNBOUND)
    Series Note
    Correspondence is mainly of a professional nature. Topics discussed in the letters include publications by WBL and by his correspondents, employment matters of former students, national defense matters in a general way, studies at Harvard and other places in the field of military defense.
    Correspondents are professional colleagues, persons in Massachusetts and national politics, Harvard alumni, news media editors, members of the armed services of the United States and Great Britain.
    Correspondence consists of letters received and carbons of letters sent. A substantial amount of correspondence is with various members of the Center For International Affairs at Harvard University, a division under the Graduate School of Public Administration. In 1954 WBL helped establish the Defense Policy Seminar at the Center, and he was instrumental in procuring many of the Seminar's guest lecturers such as Field Marshal Montgomery. Of interest are the folders relating to WBL's activity as an advisor to John F. Kennedy during the 1960 presidential election.
    Important correspondents: U.S. Senators Joseph Clark, Edward Brooke and Stuart Symington; U.S. Supreme Court Justices Felix Frankfurter and John Harlan; Henry Kissinger; Sir John Slessor; Telford Taylor; Barbara Tuchman.
    - American Association of Emeriti 1969, 1-1
    - American Association of University Professors 1969, 1-2
      Correspondence relates to WBL's listing in the Retired Professors Registry.
    - American Bar Association:; Committee on Rules Against Perpetuities 1959-1970, 1-3
      See also folder for Browder, Olin L., Jr., in GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE Series.
    - American Bar Association:; Special Committee on Legal Services in the Department of Defense 1959-1960, 1-4 to 1-5
    - American Bar Association: Miscellany, 1-6
    - Amory, Robert, Jr., 1956-1969, 1-7
    - Andrews, Raymond S., Jr., 1968, 1-8
      File relates to cartoons of WBL by Andrews.
    - A-Miscellany (alphabetical), 1-9
      Abel, Richard and Company, Inc., 1969
      Abraham, Nicholas 1967
      Abram, Morris B. 1969
      Achauer, Reed D. 1962
      Advancement, Inc. 1970
      Aker, J. Brooke 1965
      Allen, Layman E. 1963
      Alsop, Stewart 1958-1959
      Amberg, Stanley L. 1963
      American Legion 1961
      American Security Council 1970
      Anderson, Gary L. 1967-1968
      Anderson, Samuel E. 1971
      Andrews, Fletcher R. 1962
      Anthony, Garner J. 1969
      Appel, Eleanor, 1968
      Areeda, Philip 1959-1961
      Arnold, Alison 1960
      Arnold, Alivin L. 1970
      Arnold, Hap 1967
      Arnold, Morris S. 1968-1969
      Arnold, Thurman 1968
      Art, Robert J. 1968
      Ashby, John H. 1968
      Association of American Law Schools 1967
      Atchison, Charles W. 1967
      Atiyah, Patrick 1959-1968
      Ayer, Jack 1967-1968
    - Barrett, Esme (Mrs. Raymond Barrett) 1968-1970, 1-10
    - Bartlett, Cody B. 1966-1970, 1-11
    - Berry, Robert W. 1956-1970, 1-12
      Mr. Berry was a student and teaching assistant of WBL; corr. relates to his positions with the Defense Dept. in Washington and a subsequent position as corporation attorney.
    - Bosco, Joseph A. 1965-1969, 1-13
    - Boston Herald 1954-1958, 1-14
    - Bowie, Robert R. 1955-1969, 1-15
      Professor Bowie served as Director of the Center For International Affairs, Graduate School of Public Administration, Harvard University. Corr. concerns the Defense Studies Program.
    - The British Broadcasting Corporation 1955-1958, 1-16
    - Brooke, Edward W. (U.S. Senator) 1964-1971, 1-17
    - Browder, Olin L., Jr. (Professor) 1964-1971, 1-18
      Professor Browder was Chairman of the American Bar Association Committee on the Rule Against Perpetuities. WBL was a member of this Committee. File contains a copy of Perpetuity Legislation Handbook.
    - Browne, Roger 1955-1964, 1-19
    - B-Miscellany (alphabetical), 1-20 to 2-4
      - 1-20, Babcock, Charles W. 1965 Backus, Dana C. 1969 Bailey, David A. 1961 Baker, Liva 1968 Balch, Franklin G. 1962 Balliro, Angela 1969 Barnett, Walter E. 1968-1970 Barraclough, John 1967 Bass, Arnold Burton 1968-1970 Baumgartner, John Stanley 1970 Beall, Paul R. 1969 Beer, Samuel H. 1965-1966 Beirne, C. R. 1963 Bell, David E. 1960 Bell, L. Graeme 1968 Bell, Robert C., Jr. 1968
      - 2-1, Bender, Matthew 1970 Benezet, Louis P. 1959 Bentley, Richard 1959 Begran, Francis 1966 Berger, George 1962 Bergin, Thomas F. 1966 Bergson, Abram 1961 Berman, Harold 1961-1970 Berolzheimer, Karl 1965 Bevins, Wesley E., Jr. 1968-1970 Biddle, Francis 1960 Blanding, Sarah Gibson Blanquist, Margaret L. 1969 Bobbs-Merrill1963 Bok, Derek 1968-1969
      - 2-2, Bolich, Bryan W. 1961-1964 Book-of-the-Month Club, Inc. 1970-1971 Booth, John T. 1962 Bordwell, Percy 1955-1968 Boston Globe 1965-1969 Boston Medical Library 1969 Boston University 1967 Bowles, Lawrence L. 1968 Braham, Colin P.L. 1969 Bravenec, L.L. 1969 Braybrooke, E. K. 1968 Bregy, Philip A. 1970
      - 2-3, Brenneman, Russell L. 1965 Breuer, Ernest H. 1969 Brewster, Mary Louise 1967 Bridges, Styles (U.S. Senator) 1958 Brody, Burton F. 1964 Brodeur, Raymond A. 1962 Brown, Peggy 1968 Brown, Ron 1968
      - 2-4, Brownell, George A. 1961 Brownwood, David O. 1965 Bruce, William 1970 Brundin, Brian J. 1966 Brylawski, E. Fulton 1970 Buch, Leslie N. 1967 Buchwald, Art 1965 Bundy, McGeorge 1961 Burke's Peerage 1965 Burns, Joseph W. 1967 Burrowes, James T. 1966 Burrows, R.J.F. 1961
    - Cass, Leo J. (Dr.), Director,; Harvard Law School Clinic 1964-1971, 2-5
    - Clark, Joseph S. (U.S. Senator) 1955-1965, 2-6
    - Coolidge, Charles A. 1958, 2-7
    - Cox, Archibald (Professor) 1968, 2-8
      File relates to The Report of the Cox Commission on the troubles at Columbia in 1968.
    - Cunliffe, Marcus and Mitzi 1964-1969, 2-9
    - Cutter, R. Ammi, Justice, Massachusetts Supreme Judicial Court 1957-1968, 2-10
    - C-Miscellany (alphabetical) 3 folders, 2-11 to 2-13
      - 2-11, Cahill, Peter 1970 Callahan, Charles C. 1962 Callahan, James A. 1968 Cappall, Franklyn E. 1966 Carnegie Commission on Higher Education 1969 Carney, John F. 1966 Carr, Richard 1956 Carrigan, James R. 1962 Cary, John B. L(60-61 Casavola, Helen 1963-1968 Cass, Leo M. (son of Dr. Leo J. Cass) 1968 Cass, Victoria B. (daughter of Dr. Leo J. Cass) 1969 Catalano, Anthony J. 1965 Bolich, Bryan W. 1961-1964 Book-of-the-Month Club, Inc. 1970-1971 Booth, John T. 1962 Bordwell, Percy 1955-1968 Boston Globe 1965-1969 Boston Medical Library 1969 Boston University 1967 Bowles, Lawrence L. 1968 Braham, Colin P.L. 1969 Bravenec, L.L. 1969 Braybrooke, E. K. 1968 Bregy, Philip A. 1970 Bolich, Bryan W. 1961-1964 Book-of-the-Month Club, Inc. 1970-1971 Booth, John T. 1962 Bordwell, Percy 1955-1968 Boston Globe 1965-1969 Boston Medical Library 1969 Boston University 1967 Bowles, Lawrence L. 1968 Braham, Colin P.L. 1969 Bravenec, L.L. 1969 Braybrooke, E. K. 1968 Bregy, Philip A. 1970 Cavers, David F. 1967 Chapman, Brian 1958 Chester, George A., Jr. 1968 Christian, Michael W. 1967
      - 2-12, Chun Quan Yee Hop1970 Clark, Charles E., Judge,; U.S. Court of Appeals, Second Circuit 1962 Clark, Dorothy 1965 Clark, Mark F. 1966-1967 Clarkson, Paul S. 1968 File contains photograph of Rufus Choate. Clifford, Joanne 1967 Cohen, Milton H. 1967 Collings, L.V. 1970 Cole, David B. 1966 Cole, Philip G. 1963-1965
      - 2-13, Conahan, James P. 1968 Conderman, J.D. 1959-1971 Conlan, Mary 1968 Cook, Robert M. 1967 Cooley, Thomas M. 1962-1966 Cootes, Brian 1965 Corcoran, Thomas G. 1967 Corlew, John 1967 Costonis, John J. 1964 Countryman, Vern 1966 Crafts, Frederick 1969 Craig, Walter E. 1968-1970 Cronin, Christina 1962 Cronson, Donald 1967 Crouse, W.S. 1965 Cumming, Peter A. 1967-1968
    - Davis, Clifford (Professor) 1960-1969, 2-14
      File contains a copy of the proofs of an article by Professor Davis on "Letting the Conduct of Affected Parties Play a Meaningful Role in Resolving Disputes Between Adjoining and Concurrent Owners of Real Property."
    - Dewey, Frank L. 1964-1971, 2-15
    - Drinan, Robert F. (S.J.) 1965-1969, 2-16
    - Dukeminier, Jesse, Jr. (Professor) 1962-1971, 2-17
      File contains some amusing bumper stickers re perpetuity legislation. For further correspondence see WRITINGS AND RESEARCH: Perpetuities Reform-California and Perpetuities Reform-Kentucky.
    - Dupuy, Trevor N. 1961-1965, 2-18
      For more correspondence re Trevor Dupuy see GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE (UNBOUND): Historical Evaluation and Research Organization (HERO) 1956-1971
    - D-Miscellany (alphabetical), 2-19
      Dans, Alison 1968
      Davenport, Russell L. 1968
      Dawson, Alexandra deGhize 1967
      Dawson, J.P. 1966
      Dayton Journal Herald 1968
      DeBrier, Daniel 1963-1964
      DeMarco, Michael 1965
      Deppeler, Rolf 1963-1966
      Dias, Raven 1967
      Dickson, Brenton H. 1962
      Dickstein, Leonard H. 1966
      Donahue, Frank J. 1961
      Donahue, John 1965
      Donahue, Mary Elizabeth 1965-1967
      Donaldson, David K. 1962
      D'Onofrio, Francesco 1967
      Dow, David C. 1968
      Driver, Warren W. 1963-1967
      Dugdale, Elizabeth 1962
      Dumaine, Dudley B. 1964
      Dunham, Allison 1965
      Dunlop, J.R. 1963
      Durbrow, Elbridge 1971
    - Ehrmann, Herbert Brutus 1965-1969, 2-20
      For letters of WBL addressed to Herbert B. Ehrmann, see the HERBERT B. EHRMANN PAPERS in the Harvard Law School Library.
    - Elliott, William Y. (Professor) 1959-1970, 2-21
    - E-Miscellany (alphabetical), 3-1
      Earlham College 1965
      Egan, James F. 1967
      Egge, Warren S. 1967
      Ela, Roger E. 1963
      Elliott, Frank B. 1965-1968
      Emerson, William R. 1958-1964
      Emme, Eugene M. 1964
      Estate Tax Publishing Co., Inc. 1968
      Everest, F.F. 1969
      Evershed, Rt. Hon. Lord 1963
    - Fetters, Samuel M. (Professor) 1968-1971, 3-2
    - Fitzgerald, William P. 1971, 3-3
      Mr. Fitzgerald was a student of WBL; file relates to his third-year paper.
    - The Foundation Press, Inc. 1963-1968, 3-4
    - Frankfurter, Felix, Justice, U.S. Supreme Court 1954-1962, 3-5
      File contains correspondence with others after Frankfurter's death. For letters of WBL to Frankfurter see Library of Congress, Register of Felix Frankfurter papers. For additonal correspondence see GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE (UNBOUND): Shakespeare-Oxford Society.
    - F-Miscellany (alphabetical), 3-6 to 3-7
      - 3-6, Faillace, Marie 1965-1968 Fairchild, Florence 1958-1968 Fairleigh Dickinson University 1969 Feuerstein, Donald M. 1964-1965 Field, Richard H. 1970 Fiflis, Ted J. 1961-1967 Fink, Michael I. 1970 Finkbeiner, Fern 1965-1966 First Parish in Weston, Mass. 1968 Fisher, S. G. 1968 Fishman, David H. 1969 Flack, Harvey 1963 Flanzraich, Neil William 1968 Flynn, Patricia A. 1968